Freedom, freedom, freedom, oy!
There's no denying it, the future's crazy.
Oh, well, don't want to stand out.
Freedom, freedom, freedom, oy!
There's nothing crazy about it.
It's just Freedom Day.
So, what is Freedom Day?
Sounds like some kind
of feminine hygiene product.
No. It's a fabulous, crabulous day!
If you want to do something, you do it,
and to spleck with the consequences!
You know, like how I live every day.
Happy Freedom Day!
Oh, I think my wrist is broken.
Of course, it wouldn't be Freedom Day
without the traditional freedom tub.
- Ooh.
- Wow, baby.
Mm, that'll feel nice
on my shattered bones.
Wow, nude hot-tubbing?
That's all I need to hear
about Freedom Day.
Then consider
the following lecture a bonus.
On Earth, freedom is a given.
But on my planet,
we have to suffer for it.
Sure, you can be a comedian
instead of a doctor,
if you want your parents
to roll over in their graves!
Sure, you can vote for Shknadel,
if you want there should be a recession!
Sure, you can go to medical school,
if you've given up
on your dream of being a comedian!
That's why I love Earth.
You can do what you want
and no one makes you feel guilty
because no one cares.
We're not listening!
That's what I'm talking about.
Freedom, freedom, freedom, oy!
Excuse me, coming through!
Freedom Train arriving on track one.
- Ow, you broke my foot!
- Freedom!
What's this next float, Linda?
Representing our men, women
and children in uniform,
it's Earth's greatest space hero,
Zapp Brannigan.
Happy Freedom Day, ladies.
Come on, let loose and show me something.
Anything. Seriously, I'd take an armpit.
Oh, yeah. Thank you, Linda.
You're welcome!
Okay, Morbo, now it's your turn.
If that is your Freedom Day wish...
Thank you, Secretary of Transportation.
My fellow Earthicans...
We enjoy so much freedom,
it's almost sickening.
We're free to choose which hand
our sex-monitoring chip is implanted in.
And if we don't want to pay our taxes
why, we're free to spend a weekend
with the Pain Monster.
See you April 15, folks!
Cue the fireworks guy.
- Ooh...
- Ah...
Incidentally, tonight's
Freedom Day celebration
is brought to you by
Shankman's Rubbing Compound.
When something needs rubbing,
think Shankman.
Yeah, Shankman!
It costs a little more, but it's worth it.
Our planet has been through
so much this past year,
wars, droughts, impeachments,
but we've never lost our sense
of what's truly important,
the great taste of Charleston Chew.
And now, let us salute
that beloved symbol of freedom, our flag,
Ol' Freebie.
I'm swelling with patriotic mucus.
In our darkest hour,
we can stand erect
with proud, upthrust bosoms...
Anyone who laughs is a Communist.
...knowing that,
with a shifty glance skyward,
we will see by the rocket's red glare
that our flag is still there.
It's gone!
Yes, fellow patriots, I ate your flag!
And I did it with pride.
For to express oneself by doing a thing
is the very essence of Freedom Day.
Bless this planet
and all its wonderful people.
Kill him!
Kill the traitor!
Hey, it's the guy who desecrated our flag!
Stop that Red menace!
Oh, I'm all scuttled out.
What?
My planet's embassy?
They're paid to not kill me.
I thought I understood this world.
I thought I was fitting in.
But I guess I don't belong here
any more than I do
on our crappy home planet.
Ooh, sorry.
What, sorry? Our planet stinks.
We all know it.
Enough with the persecution, I'm saying.
Zoidberg, as Ambassador,
I promise you the full support
of our government already.
Poor boy. You want maybe a nice mug cocoa?
Ambassador Moivin,
you and your staff are so kind.
I am truly humbled.
What, no marshmallows?
Let's storm the place!
Without my prior knowledge.
Coming through,
Freedom Train, step aside.
You, too, Fatso, freedom!
Cool your jowls, Nixon.
You may not like it that
Dr. Zoidberg desecrated a flag.
You may even find the image
of it festering in his bowels
somehow offensive,
but the right to freedom of expression
is guaranteed by the Earth Constitution.
Maybe so.
But I know a place where
the Constitution doesn't mean squat.
The Supreme Court hereby accepts
the case of Earth v. Zoidberg.
Sock it to 'em!
Two, four, six, eight,
eating the flag is bad.
Now, your noose knot
has exactly seven twists.
You can eat my dog
You can eat my truck
But you eat my flag
and you're out of luck
She's a-waving proud around the world
From Dallas to Fort Worth
Let me say it again...
Don't mess with Earth!
They sure hate Dr. Zoidberg.
Posers. I was hating Zoidberg
before it was cool.
Where are we ever going to find
a lawyer to take his case?
I'll ask the head of the ACLU,
once he's done singing.
Don't mess with Earth
Kill Zoidberg! Good night!
Howdy there.
I'm a lawyer, and I'd like
to help your friend out of this pickle.
Who are you, old man?
Name's Old Man Waterfall,
but most folks just call me "Old Man."
I'll never remember that.
I'm a veteran of three dozen wars.
Name a body part and a planet
and I've taken a bullet in it, on it,
all to keep our flag flyin' free.
And you want to defend Zoidberg?
Are you familiar
with the old robot saying...
"Does not compute"?
Son, to me, a robot's just a garbage can
with sparks coming out of it.
The sparks keep me warm.
I don't condone what Dr. Zoidberg did
but I'll fight tooth and nail
for his freedom to do it.
Or, I would, if I hadn't lost
my teeth and nails
on Mars and Saturn, respectively.
Wait, you're a lawyer? You're hired!
You okay there in the Embassy, Zoidberg?
No. There's no cocoa marshmallows.
And every night, the rats eat
a little more of my foot.
Oyez, oyez, oyez.
All rise for the Honorable Chief
Justice Myrtle Fu
and the Associate Justices.
Counsel, you may address
the court on behalf of Earth
if you're ready.
I was hatched ready.
Honorable Judgeheads,
yonder crawdad done et up our flag.
I was doing freedom of speech.
Earth's most sacred right.
Your Honor, freedom of speech
applies to what comes out of a mouth,
not what goes in.
Can Counsel cite precedent?
Uh, yes, darlin', I can.
In State of Alabama
vs. Giant Space Iguana,
chewing the corners off the Constitution
was deemed nonprotected speech.
He shut you up, O'Connor.
Mr. Waterfall,
you may now present arguments
on behalf of Dr. Zoidberg.
Oh, God, I'm nervous.
Two of my three hearts are having attacks.
Court's kind of fun
when it's not my ass on the line.
Nachos?
Oh, Land O' Goshen.
Your Honors, I'm not
some slick, big-city lawyer
like my opponent here...
...but I am a veteran
who has fought for his planet.
You see this hand of mine?
Yes, I do.
No, you don't, 'cause I lost my real hand
planting the flag
when we took back Halley's Comet.
Yet it was worth it,
so much do I love that flag.
Aw...
I love it even more
than I love my seven wives.
That's right, I'm a polygamist.
Yet I would gladly eat a flag myself,
had I not used my intestine as a rope
to hoist a flag made of my own skin,
if it would protect the freedoms
of the proud people
who salute that flag.
Freedoms such as polygamy.
I rest my case.
Whoa, geez.
The Justices and I will now confer
using high-speed telepathy.
By a vote of six to three,
we find that flag-eating
is not protected by the Constitution.
Six to three? I beat the spread.
The court orders
an immediate public apology.
Apology accepted.
Just don't let it happen again.
She means you, you turkey of the sea.
Me, apologize? Never!
I came to this planet to learn
the meaning of freedom!
But I say it's you
who should get a nice lesson!
So, do your worst, because
no punishment could be bigger
than denying me my freedom!
You are hereby sentenced to death.
Wait, let me finish!
Also, in a rare double-whammy decision,
the court finds polygamy constitutional.
I can't wait to tell my husband.
Remember, men, take him alive,
so there's something left to kill.
Stay back!
This Embassy is sovereign mud
of the mud planet Decapod 10.
Invading these mud premises
is an act of war!
Yeah? Well, what are you going
to do about it, shrimpy?
You want to see, Mr. Bigshot?
Attack Earth!
Yes, I know it's a shlep, just do it!
A-ha! Now the rubber band's
on the other claw!
Ready? Retreat!
Shh!
Deny my freedom, will you?
Well, we'll do to you
what we did to the Squash Men
of the Squash Planet,
squish them!
- Charleston Chew?
- You bet.
All right, Kif, let's show these freaks
what a bloated, runaway
military budget can do.
Bring me the activation codes
for our global defense network.
Aye, aye, sir.
Commence lip identification scan.
No tongue.
Mm...
We can't be too careful with these codes.
Rumor has it, a double agent
may be aboard this very ship.
I'm watching you.
You, Ensign, what's your name?
Hugh Mann, sir.
Hugh Mann.
Now, that's a name I can trust.
Run down to the central battle computer
and enter these codes, chop-chop.
Um, sir, there's something
about that Ensign...
You're damn right there is.
That strapping young lad's
gunning for your job,
and he just might get it.
The enemy approacheth.
Lieutenant, fire missile one
and recommend me for another medal.
Make it gaudy, I'm going clubbing later.
Tick-tock.
Sir, all planetary defenses
have been disabled.
Perhaps the Decapodians
acquired our secret codes.
Somehow.
Well, Kif, stand by to take the blame.
Steady... Steady...
Now!
Dr. Zoidberg,
how can you claim to love freedom
and then enslave all of Earth?
Bah! Your planet doesn't deserve freedom
until it learns what it is
to not have freedom.
It's a lesson, I say.
Ow!
What the hell is this dirt pile
we're building, anyhow?
None of your beeswax, slave.
You'll find out soon enough.
Just focus on globbing that mud.
Glob!
I'm not good at being a slave.
I'm thinking about graduate school.
You know, to become a barber.
This can't go on.
Today is the day we fight back!
It's already 10:00.
Oh, you're right.
Tomorrow is the day we fight back.
Yeah? Well, good luck, sister.
All our modern technology is useless.
I know I am.
Hey, wait. I'm having one of those things.
You know, a headache with pictures.
An idea?
Back in my day,
we didn't have your fancy
all-digital weapons,
but we still managed
to kill each other just fine.
Ah, the crossbow.
A pitiless, elegant killing machine.
The Bender of the 15th century.
Not big enough.
We need something that can
take out an entire army.
Something you could commit
a war crime with...
Ow.
Earth's slaves,
behold the fruit of your labors...
The Mobile Oppression Palace!
Neat.
I don't need to tell you
that occupation forces are expensive.
But with the Mobile Oppression Palace,
a few dignitaries can
oppress your entire planet
for pennies a day.
Warships dismissed!
Do your worst you sea devils!
I'll make my stand with Ol' Freebie!
You can crush me,
but you can't crush my spirit!
Ah! My spirit!
Great-Grandpa, no!
Another victim of
the manocentric male-ocracy.
Ambassador Moivin, you killed my lawyer.
You're welcome.
He defended my freedom
when no one else would.
He was a good and honorable man.
I request a satanic funeral.
Is it possible that all this
slavery and oppression
is shmutzing up our freedom lesson?
Oh, take a pill, Zoidberg.
Begin again with the crushing!
You haven't won yet, Moivin.
You didn't expect us
to even go to a museum,
much less steal this ancient
heat-seeking missile.
I don't even know you.
Oh, it's going to make such a mess.
This is your secret plan?
Meh!
Heat-seeking missiles are useless
against the Mobile Oppression Palace.
All Decapodian technology
is cold-blooded, like us.
All eyes on Zoidberg!
Ew!
Hey, I need that to smoke!
Zoidberg, how could you?
I used to think you were cool.
Wait, people of Earth, listen.
Yes, I'm desecrating a flag,
but to preserve the freedom it represents.
Blech!
Zoidberg, you set us free!
I feel like I could stand to hug you.
I can't, but you know
what I'm trying to say.
Zoidberg! Zoidberg! Zoidberg!
Ah, if only they appreciated
freedom this much
on my home planet.
Wait a second, they do!
Because this is my home planet.
And now, to raise
this beautiful new flag,
a red lobster that won't ruin your dinner,
Dr. John Zoidberg!
You're a nice man, Nixon.
Dr. Zoidberg, how's about you take a bite
of the flag for tomorrow's papers?
Oh, I couldn't.
No, no, go ahead.
You've earned it.
Well, maybe just a taste.
Mm...
Now, that's a grand old flag!
I wonder what
the Shroud of Turin tastes like.
Freedom.